// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which type of JavaScript language is",
    answer: "Object-Based",
    options: [
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Object-Based",
      "Assembly-language",
      "High-level"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    answer: "immediate if",
    options: [
      "Alternative to if-else",
      "Switch statement",
      "If-then-else statement",
      "immediate if"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
    answer: "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
    options: [
      "Conditional block",
      "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
      "both conditional block and a single statement",
      "block that contains a single statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:?",
    answer: "Ignores the statements",
    options: [
      "Shows a warning",
      "Prompts to complete the statement",
      "Throws an error",
      "Ignores the statements" 
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
    answer: "The local element",
    options: [
      "Global variable",
      "The local element",
      "The two of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
    answer: "Function/Method",
    options: [
      "Preprocessor",
      "Triggering Event",
      "RMI",
      "Function/Method"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
    answer: "Mutable variable",
    options: [
      "Mutable variable",
      "Dynamic variable",
      "Volatile variable",
      "Immutable variable"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
    answer: "Both 0x and 0X",
    options: [
      "00",
      "0x",
      "0X",
      "Both 0x and 0X"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: " In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error?",
    answer: "Division by zero",
    options: [
      "Syntax error",
      "Missing of semicolons",
      "Division by zero",
      "Missing of Bracket"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
    answer: "valueOf()",
    options: [
      "toString()",
      "valueOf()",
      "toLocaleString()",
      "toPrecision()"
    ]
  },

];